alvicreatives.com 2016-10-15

# Alvicreatives,Web Design in Atlanta,GA. Privacy Policy

In a world where every day the security of Internet users is at stake, we have found the key to success in the same field by keeping a strict Privacy Policy. We understand exactly how vital it is to protect your privacy and our Privacy Policy would assure you that we take the highest precautions to protect your information from falling into the wrong hands.

Your security – our priority

Internet services require you to provide us with a lot of information and we know how absolutely vital security is for you. As we value your trust, we make sure that your information remains secured with us.

• We maintain procedural, physical and electronic precautions to protect our customer's information.

• We limit access to Customer Information to only those employees who need to know your information to provide Internet services to you or to maintain your website.

• We continually import new technology for the protection of your information and upgrading our systems on a regular basis.

What sort of information we require?

We may ask you for non-public personal information about you or your business from the following sources:

• Information regarding your transactions with our affiliates, others, or us.

• Information that we may receive from you and other forms or visits to our Internet website.

What do we do with the information that you give us?

• We provide products and services to you with the information that you give us.

• We are able to identify other products and services that we feel might be useful to you and your business

• We will safeguard and protect the information that you give us against unwanted intruders.

Information to third party disclosure

It is our policy never to disclose any customer’s information to any third party nor do we disclose or sell non-public information to anyone else except as permitted by law.

Even if you close your account with us, we will continue to treat your information in the same way as we do for our existing clients.

Firewalls and activity logs

Firewalls analyze the source and destination addresses and the traffic type to ensure that only authorized users have access to our systems. Firewalls and activity logs are extra mechanisms that are used to protect your privacy. Specific information given by you also helps us to investigate activities that appear suspicious and to protect our systems and your information.

Get updated on our Privacy Policy

As an existing client and upon request we will provide you with any updates or changes that may take place in our Privacy Policy.
